Previously on Reacher...
She sent Anna an address.
[Russell] First floor is
an abandoned restaurant.
Looks like it's under
some kind of renovation.
[Reacher] That's where
we're headed to next.
-[glass shatters]
-[grunts]
I got a GSW to the chest!
Check in on Russell Plum.
Tell him
I'm sorry I left him at the library.
The night my sister died,
she had a jump drive
with a decades-old photo.
General Putra wants to take
a photo with the two of us.
[Ahlquist] The whiteboard was
in the background, out of focus.
Newly developed AI can essentially
refocus the lens.
It's working.
[Ahlquist] It contains the formula
for a chemical weapon
of mass destruction.
[groans]
You send a suicide bomber
with that stuff strapped to him
into Times Square,
he'll kill everyone
within a ten-block radius.
Make enough to kill thousands.
Lila's auctioning off the drive
on the dark web
at 10:00 a.m. tomorrow.
They're gonna kill people tonight
to prove it works.
When I said Delta hunted down
and took out General Putra,
I was the one who pulled the trigger.
The woman calling herself Amisha
saw me do it.
They're hitting here. Where are you?
This is happening now.
Right now, they don't know we know.
Our best chance is
to neutralize the attack.
-How?
-[yelling]
[explosion]
[people screaming]
-[tense music playing]
-[siren wailing]
[people screaming]
[shouting indistinctly]
-[glass shatters]
-[screaming continues]
-[security guard] Freeze, asshole!
-[gun slide racks]
-Don't fucking move!
-[horn honking]
[tires screeching]
Get in!
[exciting music playing]
[Reacher] Go! [grunts]
[gunshots]
[bullets thudding into van]
What the hell happened?
Sampson tackled the bomber into the river.
The water stopped the toxin
from aerosolizing.
Sampson's dead.
Shit.
He saved a lot of lives.
[Reacher] Temporarily.
No one's gonna buy that bomb
unless they see that it works.
Lila and Amisha will try again.
And we have no idea where.
Tomorrow's morning commute,
like we thought.
Maybe something else.
I don't know, but it's gonna happen soon.
We have to tell someone.
Who? They're gonna blame us for this.
We're at the site of the bombing
and then take off in a van
after we sent all those cops
to the concert for nothing?
They're gonna think
we did that as a distraction.
We got to ditch this van.
[suspenseful music playing]
Find me a busy restaurant.
-[horn honks]
-[indistinct chatter]
-[siren wailing]
-[indistinct radio chatter]
-[helicopter whirring]
Ma'am, we're gonna need
to get you out of here
in case of a second attack.
[melancholy music playing]
There was a crew
shooting video of the event.
I want to see every frame
before the police get ahold of it.
We don't know who we can trust,
and I'm not gonna let anyone bury this.
We're gonna find who killed John...
...and we're gonna make them fucking pay.
[car alarm chirps]
[Tamara] It's been too long.
I don't like him doing this.
He's least likely to draw attention.
He's small-town, but he's capable.
You know he intends
to kill Lila and Amisha,
or whatever the hell
their names really are.
Good.
Better world without 'em.
Yeah, well...
it's hard to go back to Mayfield
after you body someone,
even if they deserve it.
They already killed Anna and Ben.
They shouldn't get to take his life, too.
I didn't want him involved
in the first place.
[vehicle approaches]
[Reacher] That's him.
Good choice.
Popular car, dark color.
We won't stand out.
So glad I'm a good car thief.
[Reacher] Head to D.C.
-Plum's loft?
-Feds and local cops will have
pulled the place apart by now.
Plum's in the hospital.
We'd have no reason to go back.
Last place anyone would look.
Keep it under 70.
We get pulled over, we have a problem.
Copy that.
[weatherman] ...multiple inches
of rain per hour,
with even heavier downpours overnight.
We're also tracking
a high number of lightning strikes
within the leading edge of the system,
and that's expected to increase
as the storm approaches the city.
-[groans]
-We'll continue updating this
throughout the evening, so keep it here
as we track tonight's
unseasonably strong summer storm.
-[news program theme plays]
-Oh, shit.
[news anchor] Just in,
we have more on the attack
that killed North Carolina representative
and recently-announced
presidential candidate John Sampson.
-Shit.
-A camera crew covering
the Feed America event at the waterfront
caught this footage
-of Congressman Sampson...
-[straining]
...tackling the suicide bomber
into the water...
-[grunts in relief]
-...sacrificing himself
to save countless lives.
We caution that
this footage is disturbing.
[indistinct chatter]
[Sampson yelling]
[loud splash]
[explosion]
[people screaming]
[news anchor] Congressman Sampson's
widow, Elspeth Sampson,
is asking that anyone with information
about this man, or his accomplices,
to please reach out directly
to Congressman Sampson's
head of security at this number.
[tense, percussive music playing]
"Tomas Waberi."
[groaning softly]
[straining]
[panting]
-[groaning]
-[monitor beeping]
[panting]
[groaning]
Oh...
Okay.
[groans]
[yells]
Shit.
Okay.
[groans softly]
[panting]
[grunts, yells]
[groaning]
The fuck?
Excuse me.
Help me to get him into bed.
[Russell groaning loudly]
You just had surgery.
What in God's name
-were you trying to do?
-[groaning]
Who you trying to call?
[groans]
[panting]
[Docherty] I ain't on
the wrong side of all this.
Jacob Merrick asked me
to come here and check on you.
He said he's sorry
he left you at the library,
whatever the fuck that means.
What's going on?
[labored breathing]
[faintly] Tomas... Waberi.
You were trying to call him?
No. That's...
the suici... [wheezes]
...suicide bomber.
[groaning]
Are you sure about that?
I'm sure.
I'm s-- [groans]
[Docherty] Okay.
-I'll take it from here.
-Okay.
You did good, Plum.
[Russell exhales]
[whimpers, groans]
[intense music playing]
[sirens wailing]
[SWAT officer] Clear!
[SWAT officer 2] Clear!
-[SWAT officer 3] Clear!
-Damn.
[SWAT officer 4] Clear!
[SWAT officer] Clear!
[indistinct radio chatter]
Shit.
[phone ringing]
Docherty, what up?
Your boy Plum pointed us
to the guy who killed Sampson.
Russell's okay?
He's jacked up, but alive.
Nearly ripped himself apart
trying to get us the name of the bomber,
Tomas Waberi.
Now, we ran it down.
He rented a car when he landed.
Rental agency used GPS
to trace it to a warehouse.
Car was in the lot, but place was empty.
Only thing they left behind was
a sealed, 45-gallon drum
with a dead kid inside.
Never seen anything like it.
They tested the toxin on him.
Anything pointing to where they went?
Credit card that bought
Waberi's plane ticket picked up 13 more
for a red-eye tonight,
two first class, 11 coach.
Lila and Amisha are first class.
The other 11,
figure a computer expert,
a chemist,
maybe an explosives guy to rig the vest.
The rest are trained killers.
Reinforcements brought in
when things went to hell.
[Docherty] Well, we're tracking down
the names they'll be flying under.
It's gonna be all hands on deck at PHL.
They won't show.
-Why not?
-'Cause the attack failed.
They didn't prove to bidders
their chemical weapon works.
Tell that to fish in the Delaware.
Better yet, tell that to John Sampson.
Trust me,
these assholes proved their point.
Their point was to demonstrate
a chemical weapon
that's effectively lethal outdoors.
They aren't going anywhere.
[Docherty] They got what they came for.
All that's left for them is
to get out of Dodge and cash in.
When they arrive at the airport,
we'll be waiting.
Just keep your heads down
until we got 'em in custody.
You were there
when a congressman exploded.
Everyone thinks you're working with 'em.
-Don't be a fucking hero.
-[phone beeps off]
Are you 100% on Lila
and Amisha not running off?
Pretty much.
Well, we need to find them,
'cause the cops aren't looking.
They could be anywhere.
Not anywhere.
They need somewhere
they can cook the poison.
Somewhere they can pivot to quickly,
a place no one would think they'd go.
[tense music playing]
Fuck.
They're doing what we're doing.
Circling back to where
the cops already looked.
The vacant restaurant building?
Turn around.
♪ ♪
[tense, ominous music playing]
[quiet chatter]
First batch is good.
Another hour and we'll have what we need.
Great.
Can't let Amisha down, yeah?
♪ ♪
[in Indonesian] One hour.
Any luck?
Crop duster rental 25 miles
outside the city.
Perfect for our needs.
Storm's coming.
Rain'll tamp down the poison cloud,
limit casualties.
Forecast says it'll blow over
by rush hour.
Relax. Tomorrow, we'll be rich.
[in English] Hey. Give it to me.
When he's finished,
put a bullet in his laptop.
I can just delete the hard drive.
We need to be certain
no one has the formula but us.
[wind whistling]
[thunder rumbles in distance]
[Jacob] When Ben was little,
I taught him to count the seconds
between thunder and lightning
and divide by five.
That's how many miles away the storm is.
And that way,
he knew the thing that scared him...
...wasn't as close as he thought.
He must have been so scared...
for so long at the end.
The thing that terrified him was
right there in the room with him.
[thunder rumbles]
Hey.
You go in there blind with hate,
you're gonna be the first one to die.
Get your head on right.
Okay?
[panting]
-They're in there.
-You saw 'em?
From what I could make out
through the cracks in the plywood.
Saw Lila walk by
and about a half-dozen goons.
Who cares? They're in there.
We have the element of surprise.
It's 13 to three.
Be nice to have some backup.
[Reacher] We're still very wanted.
There's no way law enforcement's
gonna take personnel
off the airport setup on our say-so.
What about Elspeth Sampson?
Could she make 'em listen?
Doubt she'd take my call.
But if she did, and if she believed us,
there's no way they'd risk
pulling Feds off the airport
after they learned
who she got the tip from.
We're on our own.
[dramatic music playing]
-Ready.
-Here.
What about you?
I'm gonna get my own.
[thunder crashes]
[pulsing music playing]
One, two, three, four,
-five.
-[thunder crashes]
One, two, three, four,
-five.
-[thunder crashes]
[Reacher grunts]
[sighs]
♪ ♪
[tense music playing]
I'll check the fuse box.
[thunder crashing]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[choking]
[loud clunk]
It's okay.
Power loss brings the elevator
back to the lowest floor.
I'll go up and draw
as many as I can to me.
You two kill who's ever left behind
and get whatever poison that's
already been made out of here.
How you gonna draw 'em up?
I'm gonna get their attention.
They'll see you in there.
I'm not going inside.
[intense, dramatic music playing]
[in Indonesian] The Betsy Ross Bridge
looks promising.
If traffic is jammed,
people have no way to escape.
What about this section of I-676?
It's longer.
Higher death count.
[thunder crashes]
[elevator clanks]
[in English] Go see who it is.
[exhales]
[panting]
[tense music playing]
[rattling]
♪ ♪
That's our cue.
Find out what the hell that was.
Reacher.
Lila.
[in Indonesian] What did I tell you
on the bridge?
We cannot spend our money if we are dead.
We are paying these men a fortune
for a reason.
[in English] You. Go find Reacher.
How will I know him?
He's the one killing everybody. Go!
[intense, percussive music playing]
[panting]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[heavy thud]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
Cover me!
Three, two, one.
Stop! You hit the toxin, we all die!
Give me that!
-What is it?
-It has mercury fulminate
for the suicide vest.
[chemist] Now go get the toxin.
Oh, f...
Don't let her kill me.
[yelps]
[grunts]
He's out.
[grunting]
[yells]
-[clicks]
-Fuck.
[groaning]
[grunting, yelling]
[Jacob yelling]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[racks shotgun]
Fuck!
Ah!
[grunting]
[racks shotgun]
[mouthing]
[gasps]
[grunting]
[cries out]
[straining]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[panting]
Let's go, asshole.
No!
-[beeps]
-[line ringing]
What the hell's happening down there?
The chemist is dead.
Take whatever toxin we have,
find a crowd and use it.
A nightclub.
I thought it had to be used outdoors.
-[grunts]
-It's the middle of the night.
Where are we gonna find
an outdoor crowd?
Listen to me carefully.
I need to show the buyers a body count.
Now grab a respirator and do it,
or I make sure
everyone you've ever cared about
is dead by morning!
[clicking nearby]
[soft clank]
[grunts]
Tamara.
Hey. Hey.
Hey. Tamara.
Tamara, hey. Look at me.
Okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
[thunder crashes]
[in Indonesian] Bidders are gonna
get their show.
-Let's go end this.
-[in English] Wait.
I'm just an AI tech.
You can't just leave me here.
You're right.
[choking]
This way!
Fuck.
[grunting]
No. Ah! No!
No.
[grunting]
No!
No, no, no.
Ah!
[gasps]
[screams]
[panting]
[thunder crashes]
[intense, dramatic music playing]
You should've minded your business
on that train.
People keep telling me that.
[elevator door clanks]
[thunder rolling]
[propulsive music playing]
I can't tell which taillights are his.
[Jacob] Shit, where is he?
[intense, dramatic music playing]
[grunting]
We're gonna enjoy this.
-[yells]
-[Reacher shouts]
[groans]
[exhales]
Oh, fuck!
Ah!
[yells]
[Reacher groans]
You're losing a lot of blood.
You're weakening.
Soon, you'll pass out,
then we'll strap you to a table
like we did to Anna's son.
Then... [breathes deeply]
...the fun starts.
Should've heard the boy cry
for his mother.
Will you cry for yours, too?
[grunting]
[yells]
[screams]
[choking]
[cries out]
[grunting]
[screams]
-[body thuds]
-No.
♪ ♪
[propulsive music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Hey, asshole!
You can't park there! [grunts]
[patrons screaming]
[♪ Jack U, Skrillex & Diplo sing
"Jungle Bae"]
-[lively chatter]
-♪ Right now, right now ♪
♪ Right now, right now ♪
♪ Right now,
right now ♪
♪ Right now, right now ♪
♪ Right now,
right now ♪
♪ Right now, right now,
right now, right now...
[lively chatter]
♪ ♪
[engine revving]
I don't see him.
That's his car.
Got his ass.
Philly PD! Move!
♪ Let me see your hands up ♪
♪ Everybody now,
let me see your hands up ♪
♪ Everybody now, let me see
your hands up ♪
♪ Hands up, hands up ♪
♪ Right now, right now, right now,
right now, right now ♪
♪ Right now, right now ♪
♪ Right now, right now, right now ♪
♪ Right now, right now,
right now, right now...
-[whooping]
-[lively chatter]
♪ ♪
Up top!
Put it down!
I'll blow your fucking head off.
He drops that jar,
everyone in here dies.
♪ ♪
♪ Hands up, I'll take your hands up ♪
♪ I'll take your hands up ♪
♪ hands up, hands up...
[exhales]
♪ Everybody now,
let me see your hands up ♪
♪ Everybody now, let me see
your hands up ♪
♪ Everybody now,
let me see your hands up ♪
♪ Right now, hands up, hands up,
everybody now...
We should go get that.
♪ Let me see your hands up,
everybody now, let me see ♪
-Yeah.
-♪ your hands up, right now, hands up ♪♪
[tense, dark music playing]
[thunder crashes]
[breathing heavily]
[panting]
♪ ♪
[gun clatters on floor]
[footsteps approaching]
[shoes squeaking on tile]
[panting]
[grunts]
[groans]
[panting]
[yells, grunts]
-Ah!
-[grunts]
[grunting]
I don't know what I enjoy more,
fucking you or killing you.
[grunting]
I know which one I like more.
[Reacher grunts]
[panting]
-[rain falling heavily]
-[sighs]
[groans]
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
[thunder rolling]
-[thunder crashes]
-[exhales]
[somber music playing]
Ah.
[panting]
[grunting]
[groaning]
♪ ♪
[Foster] I am goddamn impressed, Reacher.
Assume you killed everyone in there?
Looks like they got a few licks
of their own in, too.
[groans]
[gasps]
Surprised to see me?
After our last run-in...
...figured the smart thing to do
was to just...
...follow you around.
Wait for you to bring the drive to me.
Thanks for taking care of the hard part.
[dark music playing]
[groans]
[yells, screams]
[exhales]
♪ ♪
[Amisha groaning]
[groans]
[panting]
[straining]
Ah!
Your sister and nephew died
like cowards.
I will not.
Take it to hell!
[groans]
[exhales]
You're under arrest for the murder--
...for the murder of John Sampson...
...Benjamin Merrick, and Anna Merrick.
You have the right to remain silent.
-[groans]
-And anything you say
can and will be used against you
in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford one,
-one will be appointed to you.
-[sirens approaching]
If you decide to answer questions now...
-[Jacob continues indistinctly]
-[somber music playing]
[birds singing]
-[monitor beeping steadily]
-[indistinct P.A. announcement]
[snores]
[groans softly]
[Reacher sighs]
Uh...
He's risen.
Where's the drive?
Look in your hand.
You almost killed the paramedics
who tried to take it from you.
Why aren't I cuffed?
No charges.
Lots of bodies can be traced back to me.
My blood's all over that building.
Sampson's widow's not to be
fucked with.
DOD took charge of the scene,
spun a whole story about a federal raid.
Kept your name out of it.
Figured you'd prefer it that way.
I got some credit, though.
So did Jacob.
How is he?
Okay, considering.
Been trading shifts with me,
babysitting you.
How about you?
Truth?
I think we're past the point
of lying to each other.
Feel pretty good.
Better than I have in a while.
Think I'm ready to be a cop again.
What about retirement?
[chuckles]
Ask me again in 20 years.
[alarm sounds]
What the hell are you doing?
Leaving.
Sir, what are you doing?
That's not the doctor's orders.
I stopped taking orders
when I left the Army.
I'm getting Dr. Newhook.
Where are my clothes?
Got you some new gear.
New boots are on
that little table in the corner.
Get dressed fast.
I don't need to see your ass.
Doc said that big scar you had
saved your life.
Thick scar tissue kept the blade shallow.
Hadn't've been for that,
you wouldn't be here.
Lucky me.
[pants zip]
[Tamara] Oh.
Here's your sad little bag of shit
from when they arrested you.
Passport, toothbrush,
burner phone, and cash.
I threw in a few extra bucks.
You're poor, Reacher.
Thanks.
But I need another favor.
What?
I want you to get something
back for me.
[meows]
-[purrs, meows]
-[busy chatter]
Sir. Sir?
You can't have that in here!
[exhales]
-Reacher.
-[kitten meowing]
I brought you something.
-He's yours now.
-What?
Hey. [chuckles]
[purring]
I'm gonna call you Walter Cron-Cat.
Man, you do not look so good.
Neither do you.
[laughs]
You know, uh, Jacob and Tamara came by.
They told me it was over.
Not yet.
I kept telling people I'd know
what I'd do with this when I found it.
Write your story.
Get your Pulitzer.
[gentle music playing]
[kitten continues purring]
Take care of the cat, Plum.
Take care of yourself, Reacher.
Hey.
I told you the pen was mightier
than the sword.
Sword played its part, too.
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Yes.
I'll see you in 15 minutes.
[phone beeps off]
[birds singing]
-[classical music playing]
-Cream and sugar?
No, thanks.
Me, neither.
Cream and sugar's just gilding the lily.
Thank you for meeting me here
on such short notice.
Thank you for making sure
I won't face charges.
It's amazing the good will
my husband's name carries now.
All it took was him dying a hero.
[chuckles]
Washington's mostly empty suits
spouting empty promises.
Not many people there impress me.
John Sampson did.
So do you.
That's nice to hear...
...since I'm considering
picking up his mantle.
Two ethical politicians
from the same family.
Who would've thought?
Can I count on your vote?
Not registered.
No residence.
So, Reacher...
I guess
the only thing left to discuss is...
where's the drive?
Safe.
But the story is gonna come out.
Good.
If my husband had known
what was going on back in '98,
he'd have done something about it then.
I don't think he'd want
the truth buried now.
That's why he would've been
a great president.
You could be, too.
Reacher.
Springfield.
Ma'am, reporter's here
to speak with you.
Okay. Thank you.
I'll leave you to it.
Can we give you a ride?
You could.
[exhales]
[luggage cart rattles]
[quiet chatter]
You fellas waiting for me?
Our bosses sent some B-team boys
over to do a debriefing with you.
That's not gonna happen, is it?
Nope.
Look, can you just do us one solid?
We just need to put
a little check in a little box
that says we asked you
one very specific question.
Ask.
Did you receive or
come into possession of a jump drive
at any time during your final interactions
with the two women operating under
the aliases Lila and Amisha Hoth?
[tense, atmospheric music playing]
No.
Good enough.
Thank you for what you did
for the country, Reacher.
You're welcome...
McMicheals.
...McMicheals.
Jarvis.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Jarvis.
Buhner. Thanks, Reacher.
You're welcome, Buhner.
[Reacher] Oh.
Stay on the B-team.
They don't get shot at.
[♪ Mondo Cozmo singing "Sweet Forever"]
♪ I pulled myself
to the river's edge, man ♪
♪ I was looking for some sweet relief ♪
♪ And please forgive me for not knowing ♪
So you can be together forever.
♪ but I don't have the means ♪
♪ I can sing it to ya in my sleep,
it goes ♪
♪ Sweet forever ♪
♪ Hallelujah till the end ♪
♪ And it's a ♪
♪ sweet surrender ♪
♪ Until ♪
♪ we meet again ♪
♪ Until we meet again ♪
♪ I pulled myself into
that River Thames, yeah...
[meows]
[captain] For action
above and beyond the call of duty,
it is my honor to present Tamara Green
with the Philadelphia Police Department's
Sergeant Robert Wilson III
Medal of Valor.
[applause]
It is also my great privilege
to immediately reassign you
to Detective,
Homicide Division.
[cheering]
She deserves it, you know? About time.
Finally.
♪ sweet surrender...
[commander] Fire!
Ready! Aim!
Fire!
♪ we meet again ♪
♪ Until we meet again ♪
Whiz Wit.
♪ ♪
♪ I pulled myself into
that River Thames, yeah ♪
♪ I found myself some sweet relief ♪
♪ And please forgive me for not calling ♪
♪ but I don't have the means ♪
♪ I could sing it to ya
in my sleep, it goes ♪
♪ Sweet forever ♪
♪ Hallelujah till the end ♪
♪ Oh, it's a ♪
♪ sweet forever ♪
♪ Hallelujah till the end ♪
♪ And it's a ♪
♪ sweet surrender ♪
♪ Until we meet again ♪
♪ Until we meet again ♪♪
♪ ♪